That's Prince Aquasteed!
He's spent the past few years
traveling across several countries
just to further his own knowledge.
He transferred to Lapis Lazuli Academy
because he wanted to end
his travels by studying properly.
He's so passionate!
I hear he's brilliant with the sword, too.
Once again...
you are front and center today,
Prince Aquasteed.
Elliot?
I hear you have your own fan club now,
and its membership grows by the day.
Only because a foreign prince
is a novelty, I'm sure.
Anyway, did you find
the books I asked for?
Yes, in the library. There are a few.
Then let's go.
It's good that you're
as studious as you are,
but perhaps it would do you good
to look elsewhere now and then?
Elsewhere?
You've received invitations
from so many young ladies,
yet you've refused them all.
Perhaps you should
accept one for a change?
There are so many books I want to read.
There are many here that we don't
have in Marinforest. They intrigue me.
I want to be worthy of the title
of crown prince of Marinforest.
I wish for nothing else.
There is nothing else that I could...
When I saw her smile,
something in my heart made a sound.
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
A Proposal Sweeter Than Honey
I met her a year ago,
at a soirée that was held to welcome me.
It's been a long time, Prince Aquasteed.
I'm glad to see you again.
As am I, Prince Hartknights.
I look forward to studying
together during my year here.
Same. Let me introduce you
to my fiancée.
A pleasure to make your acquaintance,
Prince Aquasteed.
My name is Tiararose Lapis Clamentile.
It is a great honor to meet you.
Her courteous language,
her soft manner of speaking,
her flawless etiquette,
her polished demeanor...
The effort she'd put in was plain as day.
I am Aquasteed Marinforest.
Lady Tiararose,
it is a pleasure to meet you.
She was so dignified at all times
and spared no effort in anything she did.
Whenever she saw someone in need,
she'd talk to them and offer her aid.
She'd never pretend she hadn't seen them.
There I was, trying to be
a worthy crown prince,
while she carried herself with the
dignity of a lady of the Lapis name.
We were similar in the way we both
constantly disciplined ourselves.
But whenever she ate sweets...
The contrast delighted me.
Prince Aquasteed.
What are you looking at?
Isn't that Prince Hartknights' fiancée...
Lady Tiararose.
She's out there almost every day.
Oh? Every day?
And as I watched her every day,
my interest in her grew.
What book is she reading?
What is she saying?
What is this roaring in my chest?
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
Lately, you've been
coming here not to read,
but to gaze upon
the flowers, haven't you?
A flower... You're right.
Watching her calms my soul.
Rain...
Prince Aquasteed!
Come forth, wind,
and disperse the clouds!
Prince Aquasteed...
Why did you use magic?
You almost never use it.
Well... I didn't want her book to get wet.
I knew the truth.
I was pretending not to realize it,
but I was in love with her.
So, I wanted to give her something.
Some small happiness...
A smile.
If I spoke to her...
If I reached out, I could touch her.
She's close enough.
But I can't do it.
I mustn't.
Prince Aquasteed,
why don't you try talking to her?
Don't get such ridiculous ideas.
She is Prince Hartknights' fiancée.
I know, but...
One's first love is fleeting
and never comes to fruition.
All I'm allowed to do
is pray for her happiness.
Lady Tiararose?
Lady Tiararose!
She needs the infirmary!
What could have happened to make
such a strong young lady collapse?
Was it because of that girl?
The one who transferred in
and immediately grew so close
to Prince Hartknights?
Perhaps he'll leave
Lady Tiararose for her?
Such rumors spread quickly.
If that truly comes to pass, I...
Prince Hartknights.
I'm sorry for the trouble Tiara
has caused you, Prince Aquasteed.
Oh, no, it's not...
I'll take over from here.
It's her fiancé's job to stay by her side.
That was my first time
touching the girl I love...
My time at this academy ends
with tomorrow's graduation ceremony.
All of these restless feelings
should ease up after that.
Tiararose, I hereby
call off my engagement with you!
In that moment,
a storm welled up inside me.
No more hesitation.
I'll follow my heart...
to your side.
That is enough.
I'll take the flower I could only
gaze at before into my arms.
Are you all right, Lady Tiararose?
Prince Aquasteed?
You called?
Yes.
Send this to my father.
Certainly.
Flap your wings, break through
the clouds, and fly!
I wrote in the letter that
I would bring Lady Tiararose
back to Marinforest
with me as my fiancée,
so that she could live her life there
and want for nothing.
It did seem like things were
heading in a good direction,
but still, that was rather fast.
I feel silly for worrying over it so much.
I know. I'm surprised, too.
A new wish was born in my heart:
to make Lady Tiararose my own.
Eventually, she agreed to marry me,
and my wish came true.
Tiara's here?!
Yes. She wishes to see you today,
though her visit was unannounced.
May I let her in?
Of course, right awa—
You may not.
Not until you've finished
that pile of paperwork.
I want to see her as soon as possible!
What's he after now?
Tell me, Prince Hartknights...
What were you trying to do
to my beloved fiancée?
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Prince Hartknights...
What were you trying to do
to my beloved fiancée?
His beloved fiancée?
P-Prince Aqua...
It's all right. I'm sorry
I took so long, Tiara.
I've come to meet you.
Prince Hartknights, Tiara is my fiancée.
What? You're engaged already?
Is it official?
Yes. We have the consent of King
Alexander and Marquis Clamentile.
And...
I've informed my parents as well.
What?
So don't think you can
touch her however you please.
I-I apologize. I was not aware.
If you understand now,
I will overlook this.
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
I'm sorry for coming here unannounced.
I was just thinking
of going to see you myself.
I'm happy you came to see me.
Shall we?
Yes.
Prince Aqua, back there...
Don't. I am your fiancé.
Of course I'll protect you.
My fiancé...
I know I accepted his proposal,
but it's so embarrassing
to hear him say it.
My heart is...
Tiara.
Thank you for choosing me.
I should say the same to you.
Thank you very much.
It's like the scary version of him
from a moment ago never existed.
I feel so safe.
A whole cake packed with strawberries!
A fancy tea set!
Afternoon tea with Prince Aqua
in a beautiful rose garden!
This is too amazing!
You also like cake, don't you?
Yes!
Strawberries are a specialty of
Marinforest, your home country, right?
They're so cute and sweet
with a hint of sourness.
They go well with so
many different sweets.
I love both eating them
and baking with them!
In cakes, cookies, puddings...
Oh, I'm sorry! I lost myself!
Ever since I got my memories
from my previous life back,
I've been wanting to make
a new dessert with strawberries...
These were made with strawberries
from my home country.
I'm glad it's made you so happy.
Help yourself.
I will!
Delicious!
I'm so glad you like it.
Once again...
I am Prince Aquasteed's attendant, Elliot.
I'm not a noble, so I have no family name,
but I have been serving Prince
Aquasteed for a long time.
It's lovely to meet you, Elliot.
I am Philine Sunfist.
I have been serving Lady Tiararose
since she was very small
and was formally appointed
as her personal maid a year ago.
Philine grew up with me.
She's been like an older sister,
always by my side supporting me.
And I always will be.
I will happily follow you to Marinforest.
I enjoy serving you more than
words can say, Lady Tiararose.
Philine...
I will serve you forever.
I hope you will continue to accept me.
Thank you.
She's a wonderful maid.
She is!
Oh, I'm so happy.
So bored.
This is way too boring!
Even Prince Hartknights
won't come see me!
Why is it always Lady Tiara?
I love Prince Aqua, too!
And I'm the heroine.
Oh! That's it!
I just had a great idea!
Thank you very much.
The sweets and tea
were absolutely delicious.
I'm glad to hear it.
Tiara, this way.
Okay.
It was nice talking with the others...
but may I have some time
to talk to you alone?
Y-You're very close, Prince Aqua...
Thank you for accepting my proposal,
but I don't want it to be just for show.
Give me a chance
to ask you directly once more.
Prince Aqua...
I did sort of force you
into it, after all.
Lady Tiararose Lapis Clamentile,
will you be my consort?
Yes, it would be my pleasure,
Prince Aquasteed Marinforest.
Tiara!
P-Prince Aqua?
I'm sorry. I'm just so happy.
Tiara, I love you.
In the arms of the person I love...
It's the kind of first kiss
people dream of.
Tiara.
Prince Aqua.
You're just so adorable, I couldn't stop.
I'm sorry.
I can't! I'm gonna die of embarrassment!
But... I'm happy.
What is that light?
What's happening?
Prince Aquasteed!
Lady Tiararose!
Is this light... magic?
Could this be...
the heroine's Holy Prayer?
The Holy Prayer is a rare magic that
only one person in this world can use.
Its light, with its power
of absolute purification,
envelops the entire country,
repels disasters, and brings peace.
Only the heroine of The Ring
of Lapis Lazuli can use it.
I'd forgotten about it.
Lady Akari never used it,
so I thought she couldn't.
But... why now?
It seems to have stopped.
I'll go look. Please wait here for now.
Thank you.
Elliot is a capable attendant.
I'm sure he'll find the cause in no time.
Lady Tiararose, you needn't worry.
Just wait here with His Highness.
Every country wants
the power of the Holy Prayer.
It's not just the Kingdom of Lapis Lazuli.
I'm sure the Kingdom of Marinforest
would do anything to get it.
What if Prince Aqua comes
to desire the heroine's power?
Don't worry.
Whatever happens, I'll protect you.
It'll be okay.
The Sweetest Kiss in the World
Every country wants the Holy Prayer.
Does Prince Aqua, too?
Please, don't let go of me!